https://www.algood-casters.com/contact/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
Algood Caster Innovations acknowledges the importance of protecting the privacy of the users of the www.www.algood-casters.com/ website.
Information that is collected is used to either improve the services we offer or to improve the content of our website. If you have indicated your interest through an email, we may contact you with website updates or other relevant information. We may store contact information for future reference.
Cookies
Algood Caster Innovations uses temporary/session third party cookies solely to track user traffic patterns throughout our website. These traffic patterns are used on an anonymous basis and are not correlated with personal data of any user.
Most web browsers accept cookies automatically. You can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie or refuse all cookies. If you decide to disable the receipt of cookies from our web site, you might not be able to use certain features of the site.
The cookie automatically collects information such as a site user’s IP address, browser type, referrer and other statistical facts.
Information collection
Algood Caster Innovations collects information from various places on this site for its own and statistical purposes. We will not sell the information obtained on this site to any company or marketing group external to Algood Caster Innovations.
Links
This web site may contain links to other sites. Algood Caster Innovations is not responsible for the Privacy Statement and practices of such other sites.
Your Consent
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Algood Caster Innovations. Any changes to our Privacy Statement will appear on these pages. You are responsible for revisiting this page to review our privacy statement updates.
If you have additional questions regarding our privacy statement, or wish to be removed from receiving additional unsolicited material, you may contact us here.
About Algood
Our History
Message from the President
Staff Directory
Innovation
New Products
Circular Solutions
Product
© Copyright 2015 Algood Caster Innovations. All rights reserved
